<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Project RimFactory - Materials</name>
  <author>zymex</author>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
    <li>1.5</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <packageId>PRF.Materials</packageId>
  <url>https://github.com/zymex22/Project-RimFactory-Revived-Materials</url>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>spdskatr.projectrimfactory</packageId>
      <displayName>Project RimFactory Revived</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2033979700</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>spdskatr.projectrimfactory</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>
  Save comtability?
  - safe to add to ongoing game, though will natural gen. not happen on old map
  - remove midgame might cause problems to your safe, my most should be one time errors.


  A combination of Atlas's Materials+, Neceros Don't Burn Metal, and Argon's Expanded Materials using Project RimFactory mechanics.

  This mod is just another take on a Materials mod and is meant to be focused around Factory games like Factorio, satisfactory and more.
  It will have resources and items that fit RW from those games. and process try replicate that feeling.
  At the same time we try to use whats already in RW.

  We tried keep it simple like in factorio and not adding Too many new metals and such so far only iron/copper as new raw.

  This mod is by no mean a takeover of any of above mod, just a slightly different combination of resources and what it adds.
  We love those mods and highly recommend them if you want more in depth material lines!
  - Atlas's Materials+
  - Argon's Expanded Materials
  - Neceros Don't Burn Metal
  - Neceros Vanilla Iron and Steel
  - Cupro Pandas Glowstone mod (idea behind it)
  Used with their permission for licensing go to their modpage.

New Production:
	Digging Spot: Place this spot on light terrain to dig up clay and sand.
	Materials Refinery: Replaces Metal Refinery if PRF-Materials is installed.
		
New raw materials:
	clay: Used for Bricks.
	sand: Used for Bricks and Concrete.
	cement: Used for concrete.
	iron: Raw Iron - can be used raw or made into steel.
	copper: Raw copper.
	coal: raw coal, from the ground or from charcoal production
	Coke: coal processed under high temperatures to produce a more efficient fuel source
	Carbon: crude building material and precursor to better things.

New Manufactured materials:
	copper ingots: refined copper, ready for use in wiring and electronics
	stainless steel: Stronger and more sterile than steel
	plastic: Lightweight with many uses
	Glass: Transparent walls
	Reinforced Glass: Transparent walls that can stop (some) bullets
	coal coke: Coal heat-treated to improve the heat it delivers
	clay bricks: Your basic fired brick.  If you can build a fire, you should be able to make this.
	concrete: Basic multi-purpose building material
	reinforced concrete: heavy duty concrete for large structures
	polyester: Light fabric - better than cloth, worse than devilstrand, but can be mass-produced.
	kevlar: old-fashioned compared to hyperweave, but still better than anything you can grow in dirt.
	carbon fiber: lightweight high-strength flexible material.
	carbon-kevlar composite: interwoven carbon fiber and kevlar, a good rival to hyperweave.
	carbon plate: plates of carbon fiber laminated with plastic for use in construction.
	synthetic diamond: not as pretty as what you could dig up, but just as strong.
	
Credits:
Atlas
Neceros17
Zymex
Becris
Argon
** Without their wonderful mods, this would not exist **
  </description>
</ModMetaData>